Finding Aid for the George Alexander Heard Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Ford Foundation Papers
  - MSS: Nominations (Types of Systems & Uses - Current Draft) (Box 19)
  - MSS: Nominations (Types of Systems & Uses - Earlier Drafts) (Box 19)
  - MSS: Nominations (Public-Party Control of the Primary - Discards) (Box 19)
  - MSS: Nominations (Run-Off Primary - Current Draft) (Box 19)
  - MSS: Nominations (Run-Off Primary - Discards) (Box 19)
  - MSS: Nominations (Run-Off Primary - Earlier Drafts) (Box 19)
  - MSS: Nominations (Pre-Primary Nominations - Current Draft) (Box 19)
  - MSS: Nominations (Pre-Primary Nominations - Discards) (Box 19)
  - MSS: Nominations (Pre-Primary Nominations - Earlier Drafts) (Box 19)
  - 1950 Census (Senate & House of Represetatives; Re: Apportionment of Respresentation) (Box 19)
  - NCEW Talk, October 9, 1954 (Box 19)
  - Winston-Salem N' Paper Interview, December 19, 1952 (Box 19)
  - Duke Religion Seminar (May 10, 1951) and Unitarian Talk, March 23, 1952 (Box 19)
  - Committee on Established Lectures (Box 19)
  - The Money-In-Politics Research Project (UNC) Alexander Heard, Director, October 15, 1953 (Box 19)
  - Southern School News (1954-1957) (Mostly Re: Desegregation of Public Schools) (Box 19)
  - Papers: Alexander Heard ("Private and Personal") (September 25, 1956) (String-Bound Papers) (Box 19)
  - Rough Drafts and Related Correspondence: Nation "Eisenhower Challenges Solid South" by Alexander Heard (International News Service) (Box 19)
  - Articles: Statistic and Interviewing, Southern Politics (Box 19)
  - Southern Primaries & Elections (Box 19)
  - Michigan Conference (Box 19)
  - Correspondence Materials: Men's Faculty Club (UNC) Re: Admission of Women (Box 19)
  - Publication: Constitution of the International Association of Universities (Box 20)
  - Publication: Internatinal Congress of University Adult Education (Box 20)
  - Publication: Higher Education and Development in South-East Asia: Summary Report and Conclusions (UNESCO, 1965) (Box 20)
  - Publication: Administrative Reports (International Association of Univeresities), 1960,1961,1962,1963,1964 (Box 20)
  - Publication: The Responsibilities of Trustees of a State University; An Address - by Victor S. Bryant (Presented to the Faculty Club - Univiersity of North Carolina, October 2, 1956) (3 Copies) (Box 20)
  - Travel: Round the World: Hong Kong (Box 20)
  - Travel: Southeast Asia Materials (Includes Journal, Southeast Asia Series, Vol.IX, No.2 (Philippines) (Box 20)
  - Travel: Sweden Interviews (Box 20)
  - Correspondence: Alexander Heard with Various International Professors Re: Influence of Money Upon Elections, 1965 & 1955 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence and Related Materials: Re: Role of Money in Philippine Politics (Box 20)
  - Latin America: Re: Role of Money in Politics (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous (Foreign): Iran, Middle East; Re: Role of Money in Politics, November 13, 1964 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence (Foreign): Acknowledgements and Regrets Re: Money in Politics, 1954 & 1955 (Box 20)
  - Correspondence (Foreign): MIP (Money in Politics?) (Box 20)
  - MSS: Nominations (Types of Systems & Uses - Discards) & Introduction - Current Draft) (Empty) (Box 20)
  - Publication: The 1950 Census and the General Assembly (Gray Paper Notebook) (Box 20)
  - Paper: "Responsibility in Party Finance: Breaking the Bottlenecks" - by Herbert E. Alexander, American Political Science Association 1960 Annual Meeting; New York, September 8-10, 1960 (Box 20)
  - Journal: The Reporter, April 2, 1949, December 6, 1949, January 3, 1950, January 17, 1950 & March 28, 1950 (3 copies (Box 20)
  - MSS: Outline, The Direct Primary in the South - by Alexander Heard (3rd Draft, March 22, 1948) (Box 20)
  - Travel: Italy Materials, September 29 - October 3, 1964 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Spain Materials, October 4 - 7, 1964 (Box 20)
  - Travel: England Material (October 7 - 14, 1964) (Includes TIME (Atlantic Edition), Re: The Warren Commission Report, October 2, 1964 (Box 20)
  - Travel: Europe (London, Madrid, Geneva, Switzerland) (Box 20)
  - Vanderbilt Gazette Article: "Actions Taken on Recommendations of the Planning Study" by Chancellor Alexander Heard (No.20, September 16, 1964) (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous (Phi Beta Kappa, Vanderbilt University; Spring Meeting (May 12, 1964) and Note, May 28, 1947 (Box 20)
  - Orange Folder: (Empty) (Box 20)
  - Bound Volume: The University of North Carolina - Survey of Behavorial Science (1953-54) Chapel Hill (Box 21)
  - Black-Bound Calendar Books (2 items) (Box 21)
  - Plaque: Campaign Countdown - Vanderbilt University, June 30, 1981 (Box 21)
  - Budget Book (Box 21)
  - Daily Calendar (Wood, Unopened) (Box 21)
  - Bound Volume: Civitas (1952) and accompanying letter;; To: Mr. Arturo Nat, From: Alexander Heard, December 30, 1952 (Box 21)
  - Phone-0-Grams (1982, 1983) (2 items) (Box 21)
  - Empty Box (Cream-colored) (Box 21)
  - Black Folder (Contains Transparent Inserts) (Box 21)
  - United States Travel Road Maps (Assorted) (1940's) (6 folders) (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous -Travel Items (Box 21)
  - Historical/Theater Programs (Box 21)
  - "Political Memo" from COPE, 1961-1962 (Box 21)
  - Correspondence (Incoming and Outgoing; Alexander Heard) (3 folders) (Box 21)
  - Newpapers Clippings, 1950's (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous - Political Science, 1960's (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 21)
  - Children's Book: Little Black Sambo (Box 22)
  - Political Science Chart - "Organization of Federal Executive Departments and Agencies" (Box 22)
  - Manilla Envelopes: Miscellaneous Political Science (3 items) (Box 22)
  - Travel (Airline Tickets, Miscellaneous) (1950's) (Box 22)
  - Political Science Association Journals (Box 22)
  - Political Science Parraphanalia (Box 22)
  - Political Science Journals, 1950's (Box 22)
  - Academic Journal Articles, 1950's (Box 22)
  - Programs (Concerts, Dedications, Commencements, Awards, Etc.), 1950's (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous - Political Science (1950's) (3 folders) (Box 22)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1950's (Box 22)
  - Correspondence (Incoming and Outgoing, Alexander Heard) (7 folders) (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous (3 folders) (Box 22)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 23)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 23)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 24)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 24)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 24)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 25)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 26)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 26)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 26)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 27)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 27)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 28)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 28)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 28)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 28)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 29)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 29)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 30)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 30)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 31)
  - Box of Index Cards (Research?) (Box 32)
  - Calendar (1955) (In Red Box) (Box 32)
  - Gray Box (Contains Watch Box and Brown Leather Pouch) (Box 32)
  - Chapel Hill Telephones: Directories, 1952-1961 (Box 32)
  - University of North Carolina - Chapel Hill Student-Faculty Directory, 1962-63 (Box 32)
  - Christmas Cards (1950) (3 folders) (Box 32)
  - Journal and Attendance Record (Alexander Heard), 1950-53 (Box 32)
  - Historical Articles (Magazine, Photo Essays), 1950's (Box 32)
  - Correspondence: Air Mail Overseas Envelopes (Incoming, Alexander Heard)(Large), 1952-62 (Box 32)
  - Correspondence: Air Mail Overseas Envelopes (Incoming, Alexander Heard) (Small) (1961-62) (3 folders) (Box 32)
  - VLH Newspaper Clippings (August 1963) (Includes Mrs. Virginia Lord Heard's Obituatry-Alexander Heard's Mother) (Box 33)
  - Newspaper Clippings (1963) (Includes Alexanader Heard's Chancellor Installation) (Box 33)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Vanderbilt University, Alexander Heard and Mrs. Heard), 1963 & 1964 (Box 33)
  - Newspapers (Alexander Heard's Chancellor Invitation), October 5, 1963 (Box 33)
  - Newspapers (1964) (Includes Alexander Heard's Chancellor Installation, October 4, 1963) (Box 33)
  - Newspapers (Vanderbilt University, Alexander Heard), 1963 & 1964 (Box 33)
  - Newspapers (Alexander Heard, Mrs. Heard, Lyndon B. Johnson, John F. Kennedy) (Box 33)
  - Program: The Installation of George Alexander Heard as Chancellor of Vanderbilt University, October, 4, 1963; (4 items) (Box 33)
  - Vanderbilt Alumnus, March-April 1963; (3 items) (Box 33)
  - Vanderbilt Alumnus (September-October 1963) (Installation of Chancellor Heard) (Box 33)
  - Vanderbilt Gazette (May 22, 1963) "An Address by the President of the United States Commemorating the Founding of Vanderbilt University", May 18, 1963 (Box 33)
  - The Record (AE, May 1963) (Chancellor Heard) (Box 33)
  - Program: Scarritt College (72nd Anniversary Commencement, May 28, 1964) Dr. Alexander Heard -Commencement Address (Box 33)
  - Application Forms (Ensworth School) (Box 33)
  - Life Magazine (December 6, 1963) President John F. Kennedy Funeral (Box 33)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 34)
  - Correspondence: Invitations/Responses, 1963, 1964, 1965, 1966 (Box 34)
  - Wedding Invitations and Announcements, 1967, 1968 (Box 34)
  - Miscellaneous: Program Notes, Western Union Telegram (February 6, 1966), Etc (Box 34)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 35)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 35)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 36)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 37)
  - Correspondence: Thank You Notes to Jean and Alexander Heard, 1960's (Box 37)
  - Correspondence: Thank You Notes to Jean and Alexander Heard, 1960's (Box 37)
  - Correspondence: Thank You Notes to Jean and Alexander Heard (Box 37)
  - Correspondence: Thank You Notes to Jean and Alexander Heard (Box 37)
  - Correspondence: Thank You Notes to Jean and Alexander Heard, 1962, 1963, 1967 (Box 37)
  - Correspondence: Thank You Notes to Jean and Alexander Heard, 1963, 1964 (Box 37)
  - Correspondence: Thank You Notes to Jean and Alexander Heard (Box 37)
  - Correspondence: Thank You Notes to Jean and Alexander Heard, 1963, 1964, 1967 (Box 37)
  - Correspondence: Birthday Cards (50th Birthday of Alexander Heard) (Box 37)
  - Correspondence: Post Cards (Incoming), 1960's (Box 37)
  - Correspondence: Acceptances and Regrets Envelopes (Incoming)(Empty) (Christmas Open House, December 23, 1968) (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous: Correspondence (Incoming) Holiday Cards (1960's), Letters (1960's; one incoming to Alexander Heard) (Box 37)
  - Professional Journals and Publications (New Perspective Quarterly, 1988, 1989, 1990, Etc.) (Box 38)
  - Vanderbilt Gazette (February 8, 1963) "Chancellor Alexander Heard's First Address to the Faculties" (4 items) (Box 38)
  - Harper's Magazine (January 1971, February 1971) Re: U.S. Senator Albert Gore and "The Programming of Robert McNamara" (Box 38)
  - New Speech Materials, November 15, 1988 (Box 38)
  - Research Materials (?) Newspaper Clippings, Magazine Articles, Xeroxed Articles, Etc. (Box 38)
  - Correspondence (Incoming) (1971) (One Letter, 1964) (Box 38)
  - Correspondence Envelopes (Incoming)(Empty), 1950's (Box 38)
  - Materials: Re: Alexander and Jean Heard's Children (Connie and Steve) (Gifted Education Evaluation, 1964, 1967) (Box 38)
  - Chapel Hill Telephones (Directories), June, 1953 and June, 1954 (Box 38)
  - Index Cards: Research Notes (?) (Box 38)
  - Christmas Cards (1949) (Large Manilla Envelope) (Box 38)
  - Christmas Cards (1953) (White Box) (Box 38)
  - Christmas Cards, 1950's (Box 38)
  - Alexander Heard Interviews (Discs, I-1 through I-93) (Box 38)
  - Miscellaneous: Book Catalogues, Song Book, Stamps, Tie, Litttle White Bag of Nuts and Bolts, Etc (Box 38)
  - Research Materials (?) (Box 39)
  - Research Materials (?) (Box 39)
  - Correspondence: (Incoming)(Early 1960's and 19171) (Box 39)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Announcements, Etc. (Incoming) (Box 39)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Announcements, Etc. (Incoming) (Box 39)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Announcements, Etc. (Incoming) (Box 39)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Announcements, Etc. (Incoming) (Box 39)
  - Correspondence: Heard Family (Box 39)
  - Correspondence: (Incoming) (Includes Invitation from President and Mrs. Nixon, May 27, 1971; Swan Ball (1971), Steeple Chase (Box 39)
  - Correspondence: Birthday Cards (54th Birthday of Alexander Heard) (Box 39)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1970's (Box 39)
  - Travel Materials, July 14, 1964 to July 23, 1964 (Box 39)
  - Vanderbilt University Alumnus (July-August 1964) and University of North Carolina The Alumni Review, March 1964 and May 1971 (Box 39)
  - Program: The Installation of George Alexander Heard as Chancellor of Vanderbilt University, October 4, 1963 (Box 39)
  - Obituaries: Fred H. Weaver, Frank Porter Graham (Box 39)
  - Concert Programs (Nashville Youth Symphony, (Includes Connie Heard, Violinist), Playbills, Musicals, Etc.) (1960's and 1970's) (Box 39)
  - Stamps (Mostly Foreign) (Box 39)
  - Research Paper "Stravinsky's 'Rite of Spring'" by Jean Keller (JeanHeard?) (Box 39)
  - Leather-Crafted Book Jacket (Box 39)
  - The Thunderbird: Camp Sequoyah (Weatherville, North Carolina) (Steven Heard, 1964) (Box 39)
  - Jim Reed Chevrolet Materials (Includes Car Warrenty, Etc.) (Box 39)
  - Miscellaneous: Correspondence (Outgoing), Receipts, Notes, Etc.)(Mostly 1971, Some 1960's) (Box 39)
  - Miscellaneous: Seed Catalogue, Miniature Golf Score Cards, Stationery, Etc (Box 39)
  - The Nativity Story (Children's Book) (1959?) (Box 39)
  - Better Homes and Gardens, September 1962 (Box 39)
  - House and Garden, August 1962 (Box 39)
  - Program: No, No, Nanette: The New 1925 Musical (Box 39)
  - Publication: The Rogers Caldwell Story by George Barker (Box 39)
  - Correspondence: Heard Family (1971-72) (Within Family and Re: Family) (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Birthday Cards (Alexander Heard) (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Professional and Social (Incoming), 1971-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Professional and Social (Incoming), 1971-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Professional (Alexander Heard) (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Responses (Incoming), 1969-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Responses (Incoming), 1969-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Responses (Incoming), 1969-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Responses (Incoming), 1969-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Responses (Incoming), 1969-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Responses (Incoming), 1969-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Responses (Incoming), 1969-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Responses (Incoming), 1969-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Responses (Incoming), 1969-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Responses (Incoming), 1969-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Responses (Incoming), 1969-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Responses (Incoming), 1969-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Responses (Incoming), 1969-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Post Cards (Incoming), 1972-73 (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: (Outgoing), 1971-73 (Box 40)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 40)
  - Obituaries/Notes (Oddine Myers, 1972? and Jean Craik Read, 1973) (Box 40)
  - Baptism and Wedding Program/Memorabilia (Box 40)
  - Travel: Historical Programs, Road Maps, Airplane Tickets (Atlanta, Tennessee, Pawley's Island, North Carolina, etc.), 1968-73 (Box 40)
  - Notes, 1972-73 (Box 40)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1967-72 (Box 40)
  - Newspaper Clipping (Grateful Dead, October 27, 1972) (Box 40)
  - Receipts, 1971-73 (Box 40)
  - Programs, Playbills, Dedications, Music Concerts (Includes Connie Heard, violinist, Nashville Youth Symphony), 1970-73 (Box 40)
  - Harpeth Hall Directory, 1968-69 (Box 40)
  - Foreign Stamps (Box 40)
  - Nashville Symphony News, March 1973, April 1973 (Box 40)
  - University of North Carolina (Chapel Hill) Alumni Review, March 1972 (Box 40)
  - Miscellaneous (Invitations Lists, Empty Envelopes, Cartoons, etc.) (Box 40)
  - "So Proudly We Hail" - A Gold an Color-Etch Reproduction of The Flag-Raising at Iwo Jima (Box 40)
  - Correspondence: Heard Family (Box 41)
  - Correspondence (Outgoin) (Box 41)
  - Correspondence: Post Cards (Incoming), 1973-74 (Box 41)
  - Christmas Cards (Box 41)
  - Christmas Cards (1946, 1947) (Box 41)
  - Correspondence: Invitations, Responses (Box 41)
  - Stamps (United States and Foreign) (Box 41)
  - Notes/Receipts, 1960, 1961, 1973 (Box 41)
  - Programs, Music Concerts (Box 41)
  - "Remarks by Alexander Heard, Chancellor of Vanderbilt University" (10th Anniversary Celebration of th eConsortium Universities, Washington, D.C.), January 17, 1974 (Box 41)
  - Newspaper Clipping, August 2, 1973 (Box 41)
  - Miscellaneous (Attendance Record Book, World Book Encyclopedia Advertisement, Post Cards, Invitations, etc.) (Box 41)
  - Citizens Research Foundation Stationery (Box 41)
  - General JKH - GAH File, February 24, 1974 (Box 41)
  - Chapel Hill Telephones (Directory) December 1962) (Box 41)
  - TIME Magazine (March 8, 1963; Volume LXXXI, No.10) (Box 41)
  - Map of the U.S. "Congressional Districts for the 83rd Congress" (Box 41)
  - Calendar Appointment Pages (Box 41)
  - Microfilm #326 (University of North Carolina) (Box 41)
  - Christmas Cards (Unmailed) (Little Gray Box, "Angel Cove") (Box 41)
  - Posters of Various Lectures (University of North Carolina - Chapel Hill) (Box 41)
  - Index Cards (Research, Addresses?) (Box 41)
  - Green Index Card Box (Containing Index Cards) (Box 41)
  - Unused Stationery and Envelopes (Box 41)
  - Galley Proofs for "Southern Politics" (May 1, 1942?) (Box 41)
  - LIFE magazine (June 11, 1965, Vol.58, No.23)(Chancellor Alexander Heard, Honorary Degree, Columbia University, p. 388) (Box 42)
  - LIFE magazine (April 25, 1969, Vol.66, No.16) (Box 42)
  - TIME magazine (December 17, 1965, Vol.86, No.25) (Box 42)
  - TIME magazine (March 31, 1967, Vol.89, No.13) (Box 42)
  - TIME magazine (April 7, 1967, Vol.89, No.14) (Box 42)
  - TIME magazine (April 28, 1967, Vol.89, No.17) (2 copies) (Box 42)
  - TIME magazine (September 27, 1968, Vol.92, No.13) (Box 42)
  - TIME magazine (November 8, 1968, Vol.92, No.19) (Box 42)
  - TIME magazine (June 8, 1970, Vol.95, No.23) (Box 42)
  - TIME magazine (August 3, 1970, Vol.96, No.5)(Chancellor Alexander Heard, Academic Ambassador to the White House, President Nixon, pp.8&9) (Box 42)
  - NEWSWEEK magazine (April 24, 1967, Vol.LXIX, No.17) (Box 42)
  - Vanderbilt University Co-Ed Handbook, 1967-1968 (2 copies) (Box 42)
  - Vanderbilt Gazette (October 1, 1968, No.38 & October 15, 1969, No.46) (Box 42)
  - Vanderbilt Today (April 1965, Vol.5, No.1; September 1968, Vol.8, No.4; November 1968, Vol.8, No.5) (Box 42)
  - Vanderbilt Alumnus (November-December 1968, Vol.54, No.2; May-June 1969, Vol.54, No.5 (2 copies); November-December (Vol.55, No.2) (Box 42)
  - Spectrum (Winter 1968, Vol.6, No.2) (Box 42)
  - Vanderbilt Calendar, 1963-1964 (Box 42)
  - Nashville Magazine (March 1967, Vol.5, No.3; November 1969, Vol.7, No.11 (Chancellor Alexander Heard, "Firm and Fair," pp.2,3,4,8) (4 copies) (Box 42)
  - Nashville Area of Chamber of Commerce - "'67 The Action Year" (Box 42)
  - UTC Today (University of Tennessee-Chattanooga) (Summer 1969, Vol.7, No.1) (Box 42)
  - University of North Carolina Alumni Review (Chapel Hill) (May 1968, Vol.56, No.8; June 1968, Vol.56, No.9)(Chancellor Alexander Heard, Honorary Degree, University of North Carolina - Chapel Hill, p.3) (Box 42)
  - Cornell College Alumnus (March-April 1968, Vol.21, No.4) (Inauguration of Dr. Samuel Enoch Stumpf, May 4, 1968, Chancellor Alexander Heard, p.2) (Box 42)
  - Current Bibliography (November 1966, Vol.27, No.10, pp.25-27) (Box 42)
  - Correspondence (Incoming) Wedding Announcements (1964, 1965, 1966) (Box 42)
  - Correspondence (Incoming) Wedding Announcements (Box 42)
  - Correspondence (Incoming) Wedding Announcements (Box 42)
  - Correspondence (Incoming) Wedding Announcements (1964, 1965) (Box 42)
  - Correspondence (Incoming) Party Invitation Responses (1964, 1965) (Box 42)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Re: Chancellor Alexander Heard (1966-68, 1970) (3 envelopes) (Box 42)
  - Newspapers - Re: Chancellor Alexander Heard (1966, 1968, 1969, 1970) (Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous - Poem, Thank You Note to Connie Heard, etc (Box 42)
  - TIME magazine (December 17, 1965, Vol.86, No.25) (Chancellor Alexander Heard, "Universiites: On the Move in the South," p.94) (2 copies) (Box 43)
  - TIME magazine (April 15, 1966, Vol. 87, No. 15) (Chancellor Alexander Heard, p.82) (Box 43)
  - Science: American Association for the Advancement of Science (January 1, 1965, Vol. 147, No.3653 and April 16, 1965, Vol.1, 148, No.3668) (Box 43)
  - Folder: Saturday, October 21, 1967 (Box 43)
  - Schools, Children: Harpeth Hall, Hillsboro, Peabody (Box 43)
  - Correspondence (Incoming) Invitations, Thankyous (1967,1968) (Box 43)
  - Clippings, Newspapers, etc. (1967,1968) (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (1967,1968) (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous Bills (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous (Cards, Notes, etc.) (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous (1963) (To be filed) (Box 43)
  - Vanderbilt Alumnus (November-December 1964, Vol.50, No.3 and September-October 1965, Vol.51, No.2) (Box 43)
  - Vanderbilt Today (March 1967, Vol.7, No.1) (Box 43)
  - Vanderbilt Spectrum (Spring 1965, Vol.3, No.2) (Box 43)
  - Vanderbilt Co-Ed Handbook, 1963-64 (Box 43)
  - Vanderbilt University-Benton Chapel: Service of Worship Leaflet (February 16, 1964 & September 19, 1965) (Box 43)
  - The Graduate Faculties Newsletter - Columbia Universeity, March 1967 (Box 43)
  - The Hotchkiss School (Bulletin) Lakeville, Connecticut, 1966-67 (Box 43)
  - Philips Academy Catalogue: Andover, Massachusetts (Box 43)
  - St. Paul's School Catalogue: Concord, New Hampshire (1966-67) (2 items) (Box 43)
  - The Phillips Exeter Catalogue: Exeter, New Hampshire, 1966-67 (Box 43)
  - The Choate School: Deerfield, Massachusetts (1967-68) (2 items) (Box 43)
  - Deerfield Academy: Deerfield, Massachusetts (1967-68) (4 items) (Box 43)
  - The University Report - Chapel Hill (Chancellor Alexander Heard, Honorary Degree, University of North Carolina-Chapel Hill, Summer 1968) (Box 43)
  - Alumni Review: University of North Carolina-Chapel Hill (November 1967 & December 1967) (Box 43)
  - UNC-A Chapel Hill Newsletter for Alumni & other friends: Music Department, Spring 1966 (Box 43)
  - Maps (2 world atlases, Road Maps; Pennsylvania, Deleware, Maryland, Virginia, West Virginia, San Francisco, North Carolina, Nashville (1880's), New York, Connecticut, Massachusetts) (Box 43)
  - Travel Materials (Gatlinburg, Tenneessee; Augusta, Georgia) (Box 43)
  - Newspapers, 1963-1966 (Box 43)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 43)
  - The Nashville Tennessean Sunday Magazine (March 20, 1966) (Chancellor Alexander Heard, p.6) (Box 43)
  - The Nashville Tennessean (June 7, 1966) "Meredith Shot By Sniper" (Voting Rights) (Box 43)
  - Miscellaneous (Christ Episcopal Church Leaflet (1963 & 1967), Dinner Invitation, Incoming Correspondence (1967) etc.) (Box 43)
  - Southern Living (September 1966, Vol.1, No.8) (Chancellor Alexander Heard, pp.20-23) (Box 43)
  - Look (April 19, 1966, Vol.30, No.8) (Box 43)
  - General File (2/24/88) (In Brown Box) (Box 44)
  - Deposit Slips, etc. (3/1/80) (In White Envelope) (Box 44)
  - Correspondence (Incoming) Invitations (1979, 1980) (Box 44)
  - Correspondence (Incoming) Invitations (1997, 1980) (Box 44)
  - Correspondence (Incoming) Invitations (1979, 1980) (Box 44)
  - Correspondence (Incoming) Invitations (Box 44)
  - Correspondence (Incoming) (Chancellor Alexander Heard's Birthday Cards, March 1980) (Box 44)
  - Correspondence (Incoming/Outgoing Professional (Box 44)
  - Correspondence (Incoming) Bills, Notes (Box 44)
  - Correspondence (Incoming) Bills, Notes (1979, 1980) (Box 44)
  - Artwork Catalogue (Theo Waddington & Company, Inc.) Madison Ave, New York (Box 44)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Wall Street Journal (November 16, 1979) (Re: John Cheever) (Box 44)